<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Jorge Henriquez</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Jorge Henriquez</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>© 2019 Jorge Henriquez</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 10 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>Hi there My name is Jorge Henriquez and I’m a third-year computer engineering student at the University of California, Santa Cruz. I am passionate about technology and I strive to be nothing less than the best programmer I can be. Tech has certainly changed my world for the better and I’m certain that it can do even more amazing feats for humanity.
But when I’m not hacking on the command line, or drowning in homework assignments, I try to find the time to improve myself and my workflow.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Docs</title>
      <link>/docs/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/docs/</guid>
      <description>Important Documents Résumé  Direct Download</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Docs</title>
      <link>/showcase/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/showcase/</guid>
      <description>Bus++ A real-time web application that tracks shuttle buses, and uses statistical analysis to determine how crowded they are. Bus++ also is able to accurately predict an estimated time of arrival between a shuttle and its related stops.
Source
Slug Tour Slug tour is an open-sourced iOS and Android application meant to introduce new Banana Slugs to the wonderful world of Baskin Engineering.
Source
GoXor GoXor is an encryption method written in the Go programming language, and is based on a xor cipher in conjunction with a one-time pad.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>